

Kushal Bhuva

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Ahmedaba, Gujarat, 380015

kushalbhuva2002@gmail.com

+91-9824-8533-11

in Kushal Bhuva

PROFILE

I am currently a student of B.Tech in third year. Working in freelancing field for 4 years making posters

for clients like - $\ensuremath{\mathsf{Gym}},$ Juice Centre, and

ISA(International Society of Automation Engineers.

I have been a Video Editor from past 4 years $\,$

working on many projects that have been uploaded on the mass media and social media.

Being an budding engineer I am part of a Tech Club

Team Arrow , We have taken part in competition called

AUVSI SUAS which is organised in U.S.A and our rank

in the competition was 14th world wide.

SKILLS

Fluent InEnglish

.

Graphic Design

•••••

Video Editing

•••••

Gimbal Control

•••••

WORK EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNING

Oct 2020 - Present

I Lift Gym

· Poster designing

International Society Of Automation

• Poster designing

RedFM 93.5

• Cover for YouTube channel

VIDEO EDITING

Sep 2019 - Aug 2020

RJ Devki

• Video Editing

TedX Prahaladnagar

Voluntary Head Of Production

GRAPHIC DESIGN PROJECT

Healthy Beverages

Jan 2018 - July 2019

• Full Graphic Design Project

KNOWN SOFTWARES

- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Canva
- Davinci Resolve
- After Effects
- Premiere Pro

EDUCATION HISTORY

B.Tech

2020-Present

Nirma University

Graphic Design
Homfilic We Grow